# NEHA KHAN

FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPER

# CONTACT

- 17 Stillbrook Rd, Avon, CT
- mehakhann71@gmail.com
- nehakhan77.github.io/portfolio/
- https://github.com/nehakhan77

# EDUCATION

#### **CAREERFOUNDRY**

Certificate in Full-Stack Web Development, June 2023-September 2024

#### **BARUCH COLLEGE**

Bachelor of Arts in Business Communications, Graduated 2019

# SKILLS

- HTML, CSS, Javascript
- Python
- C#
- Libraries/Frameworks (React, Angular, Redux, Bootstrap, Django)
- Mobile Apps (React Native, Expo, PWA)
- NodeJS & Express
- REST APIs
- Version Control (Git)
- UX/UI (User stories, User flows)
- Responsive web design

# ABOUT ME

Certified Full-Stack Web Developer with an educational background in Business Communications from CUNY Baruch. Experienced in building responsive and interactive web applications with proficiency in HTML, CSS, Javascript, Python, and C#. Collaborative and detail-oriented approach from project development to production with the goal of delivering exceptional user experiences across all devices.

# **PROJECTS**

#### **RECIPE APP**

# Personal Project, Careerfoundry, July-September 2023

- Created a full-stack web application using Python, Django, and a SQLite database at the backend.
- Created responsive HTML and CSS-based pages at the frontend following the MVT architecture.
- Enabled user authentication and content creation, allowing users to post, edit, and delete recipes on their profiles.
- Implemented useful site statistics and visualizations based on trends and data analysis.

#### **MYFLIX APP**

#### Personal Project, Careerfoundry, April 2023

- Built both the server-side and client-side of a movie web application where users can browse movies, add and remove movies to their favorites list, and update their profile information.
- Utilized Node.js and Express to create a RESTful movie API to be stored in a MongoDB database and tested with Postman.
- Developed a responsive singe-page application using React and Bootstrap with several interface views.

# EXPERIENCE

# Teller, TD Bank, August 2023-Present

- Perform customer transactions including deposits, withdrawals, loan and safe deposit box payments efficiently.
- Respond to and resolve customer inquiries and concerns using standard procedures.

# Account Coordinator, Day One Agency, August 2021-May 2022

- Develop press materials for upcoming PR campaigns including media lists, pitch materials, coverage reports, and media briefings.
- Manage daily clientele monitorings for brand and executive mentions across the digital/print news space.
- Identify new press opportunities and support media outreach efforts for the Media Relations team.